With the cooperation of the delightful resort Gero Nagaraku, we are pleased to present to you another installment from Gero.
Kinkong kankong
It has begun. Hachamachan Gakuen.
Yes, I'm here.
What have you been doing all day? I'd like to talk about what I've been doing all day.
It's a debriefing.
We split up, and we've been on the move all day,
That's right.
Where did you go?
There was a theme like "In search of the ballet," wasn't there?
I got your message, didn't I?
We went to the first place,
You can eat pudding while pushing your feet.
That's great.
The pudding is made with hot water,
It's warm pudding, right?
That's right.
First of all, the exterior looks like this,
First of all, it's cute, and the back is a bath, so it's OK,
First of all, it's OK because it's a bath in the back, and you can take a picture in front of the colorful cloth,
This way, this way.
And there was a sign that said, "This is the way here,
It's so cute.
The moment you put the pudding in your mouth,
The moment I put the pudding in my mouth, it just melted and disappeared.
I almost drank it.
The last pudding.
It was soft.
It was soft rather than hardened.
Drinkable pudding.
Yes, it was drinkable.
It was delicious.
This is only the first one, right?
It was only the first one.
How many places have you been?
Five.
Wow.
That's amazing.
You've been to a lot of places. I've been to a lot of places.
The food was really good,
I had the meat sushi at Hinagiwagiri.
Wow! You wanted that?
That's what we wanted. We were too.
Do you know what natto kuton is?
Nattokuton.
What's that?
This,
Looks delicious.
This way.
Hinagi-nigiri no akami,
Marbled,
Natto kuton.
Nattoukuton.
Where, where is it?
It's pork, but it's pork belly.
It's pork belly, but it's natto powder?
Yeah, yeah.
They're feeding it natto.
Oh, he's eating it.
Natto and natto, and pigs to eat natto.
Oh, my gosh! Cute.
Nattokuton.
It's cute.
It was delicious.
I like it.
And we went there at the same time,
They make their own butter.
Wow.
I went to a place where they make grilled onigiri with cheese butter.
Yaki onigiri?
Onigiri?
Yes. There were tons of onigiri with bonito flakes inside,
I chose cheese,
I had homemade butter and cheese on mine,
And then there are butter sandwiches, right?
Butter sandwiches with berries,
A version with lots of berries.
Wow.
It was delicious too.
Ice cream?Ice cream?
It's a butter sandwich, so they kneaded homemade butter and berries into it,
It's really delicious.
Butter is pretty fatty, isn't it?
It's like fat when you eat a lot of it,
But it's homemade,
It was so creamy,
It was delicious.
It's a grilled onigiri, but it's a bit like a dessert.
It's a little bit strange when it's a grilled onigiri.
It's strange.
You have to eat it to understand.
I thought grilled onigiri was the image of Japanese food,
But it doesn't look like that.
Does it mean it's warm?
It's warm.
The container is also OK,
It's cute.
Maybe it's because it's a spa town.
Yes, it is.
Hou-chan was there.
Honoka-chan was there.
Honoka-chan said, "This way.
She sent me.
They said Honoka was here.
Isn't she cute?
What's so cute about Honoka?
Her ears are standing up.
Isn't she like Hou-chan?
Cow used to use it for her milk bath.
Is this where the hot water comes out?
It's coming out of here.
It's so cute.
It's really cute.
It looks really pretty.
We also went to a hot spring museum,
We also went to a walking footbath at a hot spring museum, and went to a frog shrine,
And we also went to a frog shrine,
You have a full schedule.
We also went to the Shirasagi-no-yu (hot spring of the egret).
I went to so many places.
We went to footbaths, food, and so on.
After you have seen so many times, you might be looking back,
I may be looking back.
Please take another look.
This is us on the first day, while we were enjoying the vomit,
We went to Takayama.
First of all, we were looking for lunch,
We were looking for lunch at a restaurant called Umamiya,
They have set menus, curry and rice, etc,
Ramen noodles, udon noodles, and so on.
All kinds of things.
You name it, they have it.
I arrived at a certain restaurant,
I was like, what is it?
Hoba miso.
I had a set meal of Hira beef,
It was on a teppan, with a gas stove like this,
It was meat, miso, and leeks.
Oh, that's terrible.
Yes, I had this set meal,
I'm Hou-san.
I'm Hira beef curry.
It's so soft.
Because I was in the footbath.
I was in a footbath and my face was so soft and smooth.
It was a footbath, wasn't it?
Yes, Hou-san had Hiragyu Curry.
It was sweet.
It was spicy, but the Hira beef oil was sweet.
Yes, it was very sweet.
It was mellow.
The father of the restaurant,
He explained everything to me.
He explained everything to me,
He explained everything to me and told me to eat the frankfurters.
First of all, he was so kind.
He said, "Once you eat a frankfurter here, you won't be able to eat it anywhere else.
He told me all the good points of the place.
That's nice.Nice.
I also left my signature, so please go there.
Decorate it.
And take pictures.
I'm glad you did.
We have autographs in all the places we went,
Please take a look.
I want you to go around, like a pilgrimage to a holy place.
It's like a crazy tour of a school.
And then, you know,
We bought souvenirs.
Yay!
I'm so happy.
You bought me a souvenir?
First of all,
I'm so happy.
I wonder what it is.
Mr. Okuro.
Thank you.
Mr. Taru.
Is this...
I want to match them.
I want to make them matching.
I was thinking "meow".
Okay, let's do it!
Tarabo!
I was just saying...
It's Tarubo!
I just got this from one of the Boo-Boo members. It's so cute, I'll take it home.
I'll leave it at home, I'm happy to see you.
I'm so glad you're home...
It's a "Boo-Boo" machine, and here it is, and I already took it, but it was the last one, and it was a capsule, but it was a capsule.
And there are these capsules, and when you take a capsule from the machine, there's a number written inside, and the oyster is a locker like this.
I got the key and it was number 14... 14... and I wonder if you can see it in the picture...
Hey, hey, it's cute! It's in there.
And it was a lot of it... so it's really sweet...
No, no, no, no... we have this bread, too.
Let's eat it later.
And the last thing I want you to see... is this... which Kimo-san asked me to take away.
I wonder if it's a girl...
I wonder if it's a girl... a girl leaguer... in the river... in the middle of the river... there's this statue...
This girl has long legs... and the opposite is a girl with long legs... and I thought it was funny to take it... this one... this one... this one... this one... this one...
Honoka, she's in the middle of the same statue, and she took this number of statues.
I see... that's right... it's not so unusual... if you play with Eta's car... and the car and the person... and the person... and the person...
I'm sure it's fun.
I'm sure it'll be fun.
We'll have some fun while we're in there.
Let's have fun!
Good morning.
It's morning of the second day.
Did everyone sleep well?
I did.
Slept well.
I woke up feeling great.
I felt great.
I woke up to the mountains.
I was so awake.
I saw them today.
It was a beautiful morning.
We're having a buffet breakfast now.
Lots and lots of your favorite foods.
I'll eat a lot.
Let's eat a lot!
Please look forward to the next video.
Mr. Ouk, I found a place to take a selfie.
I'm a gooey gooey gooey gooey gooey
But
gooey gooey gooey
Oh, I'm aiming at it
Over there and over there
It's all gooey.
Oh, it's rice
All gooey.
I like it.
Wow.
Let's see if it's in there.
Here we go.
It's not red.
Soybean paste.
Is this white?
Yes.Ha!
It's been so long since I've had them!
Even bamboo shoots are great!
I love tea.
I wonder if it's in there.
Here we go.
It's not red.
Miso.
Is this white?
White miso.
Wow!
It's so fine!
Looks so delicious!
Ingredients cut into small pieces
Looks delicious!
First of all, it's chicken, right?
It's so soft and juicy!
That's great!
Yay!
Now, let's try the others.
I want some of this!
It's so good!
I want some of this.
What do you want?
Shiro-miso (white miso paste).
It's the best.
What else should we have?
Everyone is here.
Looks delicious.
I can't wait to eat it.
Bon appétit.
Please join your hands together.
I did.
Bon appétit.
Here is the highlight of my breakfast this time.
Chicken and tofu simmered in miso.
Looks delicious.
I wanted to choose something that goes well with rice.
It's so good.
Miso.
It's so steamy, isn't it?
The steam is so good.
Bon appétit.
Oh, it's a lot of rice.
That's a lot of rice.
Of course it's rice!
Delicious!
I've been eating a lot since this morning.
I eat a lot at night, too.
I don't often eat that much out of a bowl
It feels good, doesn't it?
I applaud.
Delicious!
Yum! Yum!
May I continue?
Yes, please.
Yes, please eat.
Go ahead.
Please eat.
In the spring, I took a variety of fresh salads as the main dish.
Well-balanced
Salad.
I'm interested in
This one!
Grilled red fish with salted malted fish paste?
Yes!
I'm curious about this, so I'd like to try some.
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
It's packed with flavor.
It's got the taste of Ako, too.
Wrapped in salt cod.
It's all wrapped up in a salt cody.
Delicious!
I'll keep eating.
Please eat.
Okay, my main dish this time.Yes, my main dish this time is
The main dish for me this time is dashi chazuke, which I took a self portrait of myself!
Looks delicious!
It said to top with your favorite condiments...
I put all of them!
Everything looked so delicious!
There are so many ingredients!
Bon appétit!
The chicken is delicious!
I can eat my rice soon!
Ochazuke is the best!
Now let's proceed to eat. Here you go.
Oh man, that's a lot of tension. It's a little volume.
I am the three sticky rice brothers!
Three brothers?
Mr. Tororo. Who's the eldest?
The first one is Mr. Tororo.
The second one is Mr. Mekabu.
Looks like a horse.
The third is Mr. Okra.
I see.
How should I eat this?
I'll put three on top.
Feel free to try it.
A little bit at a time.
That's a nice breakfast.
It's very tender.
Start in the morning.
Not at all. Put them in order.
You know what?
The older one's jealous.
Bon appétit!
Looks so good!
Big winner!
Tortoiseshell eyes are so good in the morning!
Yum!
Is it good?
The crunchy texture of the turnip.
The okra's soupy texture.
I took pictures of everything.
I'm back here.
I was about to put rice on it.
Amazingly tender meat!
Delicious curry!
It's called "morning curry".
Delicious.
It's sweet.
It's so good!
It's more than just a sweet curry.
It's more like the sweetness comes from the meat.
It's like the curry is sweetened by the meat.
It's like a sweet curry.
Well, let's all keep on eating!
Let's eat!
Let's eat a lot!
It was a nice inn. Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
The hot spring was impressive, wasn't it?
Hey, really.
It's really real.
Really.
It's so thick.
But, you know, it makes my skin so soft and smooth.
Even when I wake up in the morning, how is it?
It's different. It was moist.
It's true.
A little bit more.
It was totally different.
I wish I could have used it all the time.
Really.
I was able to get a good rest.
Breakfast was delicious.
It was delicious.
Both breakfast and dinner were buffet style.
Then we all enjoyed karaoke and ping-pong.
It was a great time.
We had a great time.
They really worked hard.
Thank you very much.
It's a nice place.Lovely place, isn't it?
Let's come back.
I want to come here in private.
I want to come again.
I'll see you then.
Mr. Gero Longest Rough.
Best regards.
Please take care of me.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Today, Hou-chan and I are going to go to the location of Gero.
I'm off.
What are you going to do, Haru and Yuzuki?
Me and Yuzuki are going to go for a walk in Gero.
Maybe we'll bump into each other.
Maybe we'll meet somewhere.
When I'm on my own.
And don't forget, we're going to seek Baen.
Oh, that's right.
That's the one you forget.
If we don't remember, he'll forget for sure.
I see.
Let's send various pictures every time.
Let's deliver them to everyone.
Please take a look.
Let's enjoy the day.
I'm off.
Thank you very much.
It's time for Shachi News.
I have a happy news.
Our 2nd EP will be released on June 28th.
Yay!
This time, we asked Kento Matsuguma to write all the songs.
It's the first time. It's the first time for us to have Mr. Matsuguma write songs for us.
It's the first time.
First time in 10 years.
He listened to us a lot from the Uchiasen group,
I think we have created a very passionate song.
Please look forward to it.
We are currently on a free live tour.
We are touring in various places.
You can see our live performances for free, so please come and join us.
We will also be holding special benefit events at each location,
We are looking forward to seeing you there.
That's all for now.